targetseo.com 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy | SEO India

Your privacy is important to us. Target SEO is committed to protecting our customers information and we value the privacy of every individual who visits our Website. We have created this Privacy Policy to help you understand how we collect, use and protect your information when you visit our website.

Data Collection Use :  
We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number, address or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We do not give this information to third parties.

What do we use your information for?  
We may use such information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising message. It may be used by us for for billing purpose and process,  newsletters, clients requests, inquiries or complaints and also for other customer care related activities; and all other general administrative and business purposes. However, in these circumstances, such information will not be disclosed to any third party. It may be used by us for a number of purposes connected with our business operations and functions, which include:

1\. To improve customer service.  
2\. To personalize user experience.  
3\. To improve our website.  
4\. To send periodic emails.  
5\. To run a promotion campaign, survey, contest or other sites features.

Information Sharing:-  
We do not sell, share, rent, transfer, trade to third parties your personally identifiable information. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Cookies Beacons:-  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We utilize cookies to track referrals from internal and external affiliates, as well as advertising campaigns.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

Links to other websites:-  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users/clients  to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

Controlling your personal information  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, or delete inaccuracies by making the change within the `edit profile` tab in your account or by emailing our Customer Support at sales@targetseo.com. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

Choice/Opt-Out:-  
Our site provides users/clients the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

Public Forums:-  
Please remember that any information you may disclose in our User Directory, Forums, case studies, testimonials, or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

Data Retention:-  
We may use the information to improve our products and services as long as your account is active.We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Protecting your personal information:-  
We take all possible precautions to protect your information. Whenever you submit some information via this website, your information is protected online and offline. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete, up-to-date and stored in a secure environment protected from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. In case of any concerns the privacy officer can be contacted at sales@targetseo.com.

Security:-  
Whenever you submit some information via this website, your information is protected online and offline. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we collect. But No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Changes in Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
